Register of the Allan E. Goodman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- 1975 INCREMENT, 1956-1974 (Boxes 38-108)
  - DEBRIEFINGS, 1965-1969 (Boxes 96-101)
    - Province representative, Go Cong and Kien Hoa, Vietnam, 1965-1966
    - Province representative, Kien Phong, An Giang, Binh Long, Vietnam, 1963-1967 (Box 99)
    - Province representative, Kien Phong and Dinh Tuong Provinces, Vietnam, 1965-1967
    - Province representative, Quang Tin Province, Vietnam, 1966-1967
    - Provincial agriculture advisor, USAID, Quang Nam Province, Vietnam, 1966-1967
    - Provincial refugee advisor, Binh Dinh, Vietnam, 1967-1969
    - Provincial representative, Kien Hoa, Vietnam, 1966
    - Provincial representative, Phu Yen Province, Vietnam, 1967-1968
    - Provincial representative, Phuoc Tuy Province, Vietnam, 1964-1966
    - Provincial representative, Quang Nam Province, Vietnam, 1965-1966
    - Public administration advisor, Saigon, Vietnam, 1963-1967
    - Public administration advisor, Saigon, Vietnam, 1966
    - Public administrator, Saigon, Gia Dinh Province, Vietnam, 1964-1967
    - Rural development officer, Vietnam, 1967-1969
    - Senior AID official (agriculture), Saigon, Vietnam, (Reuben Simmons), 1965-1967
    - Senior AID official, Region I, Vietnam, 1966 (Box 100)
    - Senior AID official, Saigon, Vietnam, 1964-1966
    - Senior AID official, Vietnam, 1966
    - Senior district advisor, Di An District, Bien Hoa Province, Vietnam, (Peter D. Orr), 1966-1968
    - Senior district advisor, Ninh Hoa, Vietnam, (Henry T. Gallagher), 1966-1968
    - Senior nurse advisor, Saigon, Vietnam, 1966-1968
    - Senior nursing advisor, Phan Rang, Ninh Thuan Province, Vietnam, 1966-1967
    - Senior nursing advisor, Saigon, Vietnam, 1965-1967
    - Senior State Department consultant, Saigon, Vietnam, 1961-1968
    - Tax advisor (administration), Saigon, Vietnam, 1966-1967
    - Two AID officials, Region II, Vietnam, 1966
    - USAID agriculturalist, Vietnam, 1967-1968
    - USAID British physician, Vietnam, 1963-1967
    - USAID engineer, Saigon, Vietnam, 1967
    - USAID physician, Nha Trang, Vietnam, 1967
    - USAID province representative, Quang Ngai Province, Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 101)
    - USAID province representative, Quang Tri Province, Vietnam, 1964-1966
    - U.S. brigade commander, Region III, Vietnam, 1967-1968
    - U.S.I.S. representative, Hue, Thua Thien Province, Vietnam, 1964-1967
    - Vietnamese government official, Tay Ninh, Vietnam, 1967
    - Vietnamese government official, Vietnam, 1966-1967
    - Vietnamese physician, Saigon, Vietnam, 1968
    - Youth group advisor (education), Vietnam, 1959-1966
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1967-1973 (Boxes 101-102)
    Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
    - General (Box 101)
    - Abbey, Pamela E.
    - Ahmadjian, V.
    - Anderson, Roy S.
    - Barnett, Robert W.
    - Barsky, Arthur J.
    - Bass, Jerome R.
    - Bergesen, Alf E.
    - Bode, Karl F.
    - Bolton, Robert
    - Bouquet, Theresa
    - Bowie, Robert
    - Bowles, Samuel
    - Boynton, George R.
    - Britton, Edward C.
    - Bunker, Ambassador Ellsworth
    - Campbell, John Creighton
    - Cohen, Morris H.
    - Cohen, Saul B.
    - Colbert, Vice Admiral Richard G.
    - Colby, Ambassador William
    - Cooke, Charles
    - Crumbley, Vivian D.
    - Cummings, F. Harry
    - Cuong, Nguyen
    - De, Colonel Dinh Van
    - Djauhari, S.
    - Doeppers, Daniel F.
    - Donnell, John C.
    - Dudik, G. N.
    - Duncanson, Dennis J.
    - Dung, Nguyen Quoc
    - Farnsworth, Ben (Box 102)
    - Ferguson, Glenn W.
    - Ferrer, Elizabeth
    - Fishel, Wesley
    - Franks, Lawrence M.
    - Fujii, Takashi
    - Gee, R. Doreen
    - Ginsburg, Norton
    - Golay, Frank H.
    - Goodwin, Browne C.
    - Grant, James P.
    - Gurr, Ted Robert
    - Harris, Elaine A.
    - Harsch, Joseph C.
    - Hartman, Pierre M.
    - Hartz, Louis
    - Hien, Nguyen Van
    - Hopkins, H. B.
    - Howe, Rita
    - Hughes, Barry
    - Huntington, Samuel P.
    - Ikle, F. C.
    - Jacobini, H. B.
    - Kasperson, Roger E.
    - Ke, Congressman Khieu Thien
    - Kellen, Konrad
    - Kelly, William B.
    - Kintner, William R.
    - Knorr, Klaus
    - Koritzinsky, Allan R.
    - Laquian, Aprodicio
    - Leopold, Richard W.
    - Levitt, Jane
    - Loubert, J. Daniel
    - McVicker, Charles
    - Mendenhall, Joseph A.
    - Metzger, General Louis
    - Miles, Simon R.
    - Minh, Congressman Ho Van
    - Morris, Stephen
    - Murphy, James P.
    - Nhuan, Congressman Ho Ngoc
    - Norris, James A.
    - Oliver, Robert W.
    - Panzer, Cecile
    - Paulsen, Henry
    - Penniman, Howard R.
    - Phon An, Nguyen Khon
    - Pickering, Lawrence G.
    - Quinn, John J.
    - Rho, Yung Hee
    - Rice, Bill
    - Richards, Don
    - Rioch, Dr. David McK.
    - Rondinelli, Dennis A.
    - Rose, Leo E.
    - Saikowski, Charlotte
    - Satlow, Frank P.
    - Schuster, Alvin
    - Siamwalla, Ammar
    - Silverman, Jerry Mark
    - Simpson, Lieutenant Commander Benjamin Mitchell, III
    - Simpson, Samuel J.
    - Sperling, Philip
    - Steinberg, David I.
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert
    - Sullivan, Ambassador William H.
    - Sussman, Leonard R.
    - Talbot, Phillips
    - Temmins, Peter
    - Thanh, Le Cong
    - Thayer, Carlyle A.
    - Tien, Josee
    - Tillson, General John C. F., III
    - Tu, Vu Duy
    - Tue, Congressman Pham Duy
    - Vorster, Walter
    - Washburn, Barr V.
    - Wehrle, Roy
    - Wenzel, Robert H.
    - Withington, W. A.
    - Yeung Yue Man
    - Young, Kenneth T.
    - Zasloff, Joseph J.
  - VIETNAMESE LANGUAGE MATERIAL, 1960-1972, undated (Boxes 103-104)
    Contains petitions, books, pamphlets, periodicals, and other printed matter in Vietnamese. Also includes one item in Chinese and Vietnamese.
  - CARD FILE, undated (Boxes 105-106)
    Index card notes relating to South Vietnam, Thailand, and counterinsurgency. Arranged by subject.
  - BINDERS, 1956-1972 (Box 107-108)
    Contains biographic data sheets, notes, clippings, and a manual from the Selective Service System related to Vietnamese legislators originally housed in binders. The titles that appeared on the binders have been preserved. Arranged chronologically.
    - National Assembly biographic data, 1956, 1959 (Box 107)
    - South Vietnam Biographic Data, 1960-1967
    - Memcons, Lower House, Actives, 1969-1970
    - Memcons, Lower House, Inactives, 1969-1970 (Boxes 107-108)
- 1976-1996 INCREMENTS, 1950-1982, undated (Boxes 108-130, 135)
  Contains additional subject files, speeches and writings, printed matter, and material in Vietnamese received between 1976 and 1996.
  - SUBJECT FILE, 1967-1975, undated
    Includes memoranda, reports, notes, correspondence, and clippings mainly related to Vietnam, arranged alphabetically according to Goodman's original folder titles.
    - 1967 Census of Saigon, 1968 (Box 108)
      Photocopy of text in Vietnamese. Also included are two typescripts in English and handwritten notes.
    - 1968: Thieu's insurgence, undated
    - April - New York City, 1975
      Contains notes and correspondence to persons in New York relating to Negotiating While Fighting and a planning meeting on post-war reconstruction and assistance programs in Indochina that was to be held in New York, but was later cancelled.
    - April - Washington, 1975
      Contains notes and correspondence to persons in Washington, D.C. mainly relating to Negotiating While Fighting and a planning meeting on post-war reconstruction and assistance programs in Indochina that was to be held in New York, but was later cancelled.
    - Basic treaty, 1971-1975
    - Bibliography, 1965-1975
    - Briefing on Vietnam Negotiations (VNN) Project, 1974
    - Certifications for migrants, 1972
    - Christmas Bombing (December 1972), 1972-1975
    - Congressional documents on Southeast Asia, 1974
    - Detente and the Communists' role (Soviet Union, China, etc.), 1967-1974
    - Enquêtes démographiques au Vietnam en 1958, undated
      Contains photocopies of a select portion of the book.
    - Enquete demographique a Saigon en 1962, photocopy, undated (Box 109)
    - The Evacuation, 1975
      Contains notes and correspondence mainly written by Goodman on behalf of Vietnamese refugees trying to find work in the United States. Also includes some curricula vitae.
    - Explanations/theories of failure of peace/negotiations, 1966, 1974
    - Four Party Joint Military Team - MIAs, 1973-1975
    - Freedom of Information requests, 1975
    - Implementation - Communist aid, 1973-1974
    - Implementation - U.S. withdrawals personnel, 1973-1974
    - Interview file - future, 1971-1975
    - Kissinger statements, 1975
    - Kissinger questions, undated
    - The last offensive and the evacuation of March 1975, 1975-1976
    - Legacy of Lyndon B. Johnson, 1966-1971
    - Lost opportunity charges, 1963-1972
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1975 (Box 110)
    - Monthly economic data summaries, 1971-1972
    - The Negotiators
      - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1964-1967
      - Haig, Alexander M., Jr., 1974
      - Harriman, W. Averell, 1971, undated
      - Le Duc Tho, 1972
      - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1974, undated
      - Pham Van Dong, 1968
      - Rusk, Dean, 1973
    - Paris Agreement, 1974
    - "Principal Lines of Decision-Making on the Vietnam Negotiation in the Nixon Administration,", undated
      Contains a flowchart.
    - The Provisional Revolutionary Government, 1973-1974, undated
    - SEADAG codebooks, photocopies, 1967-1970
      Contains photocopies of codebooks for various Vietnam surveys.
    - Staffing, 1971-1974, undated (Box 111)
    - Statistics on war costs and casualties, 1971-1975
    - Thieu/gun assessment and policy, 1968-1975, undated
    - The Transition, 1975 April 28
    - "Urban Income Estimates, 1962 through 1968,", undated
      Contains a photocopy of a section from an unidentified publication.
    - Urban self-development, undated
    - United States Government (USG) assessments, 1969-1975
    - Vietnam refugees
      - Interview questions and answers, undated
      - Interviews, 1972
      - Study of migration to Saigon codebook, undated
      - Study of migration to Saigon questionnaire, 1972 June-October
      - "Survey of Refugees in Vietnam," Office of Civil Operations and Rural Support (CORDS), 1967 September
    - Whipsaw examples, 1971-1972
  - SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1958-1982, undated (Boxes 111-118)
    Arranged alphabetically by author, then by title of the work.
    - Adkins, J. H., "War Type, Population and Security: Keeping the Basics in Mind,", 1972 January 17 (Box 111)
    - Brown, David E., "The Politics of Counterinsurgency," photocopy, 1970
    - Canh, Nguyen-Lang and Luce, Don, "An Approach to Post-War Service Priorities in South Viet-Nam,", 1969 October
    - Chou, Phan Thien, "Vietnamese Nationalism: 1919-1940," photocopy, 1966
    - Croizat, Victor J., "The Mekong River Development Project: Some Geographical, Historical, and Political Considerations", 1967 June (Box 112)
    - Farmer, James, "Counter-Insurgency: Viet-Nam 1962-1963,", 1963 August
    - Franks, Lawrence, "Social Organization and Political Participation: A Study of Voluntary Associations in Saigon," thesis, circa 1973
      Includes a handwritten note from the author to Goodman.
    - Goodman, Allan E.
      - "Appendix: The Paris Agreement & Its Breakdown,", undated
        Contains notes for a section of an unidentified publications as well as photocopies of excerpts from articles and books.
      - "The Causes and Consequences of Migration to Saigon, Vietnam,", 1973 August
      - "Getting Out,", 1972-1974
        Contains mainly notes, correspondence, and material gathered for the article. Published in The American Political Science Review.
      - The Lost Peace: America's Search for a Negotiated Settlement of the Vietnam War
        - Introduction and chapter outline, 1973-1974
        - Hand-written manuscript, undated (Box 113)
          Many pages of this draft are typed with Goodman's handwritten comments and edits.
        - First typed draft, 1976, undated
        - Second revision, undated
        - Second typed draft, undated (Boxes 113-114)
        - Third revision, undated (Box 114)
      - Negotiating While Fighting: The Diary of Admiral C. Turner Joy at the Korean Armistice Conference, draft, 1978 (Boxes 114-115)
      - Notes and miscellaneous writings, 1958-1982 (Box 115)
        Also includes writings by others interspersed throughout the file.
      - Notes on Hoa binh by Nguyen Manh Con, undated
      - Politics in War: The Bases of Political Community in South Vietnam, draft, 1973 (Box 116)
    - Halpern, J. M., "The Role of the Chinese in Lao Society,", 1961 March 1
    - Hickey, Gerald C., "Some Recommendations Affecting the Prospective Role of Vietnamese Highlanders in Economic Development,", 1971 September
    - Jonas, Anne M. and Tanham, George K., "Laos: The Current Phase in a Cyclic Regional Revolution,", 1961 February 2
    - Lam, Truong Buu, "Vietnamese Nationalism from 1900 to 1918,", 1966
    - Long, Ngo Vinh, "Some Aspects of the Vietnamese Peasants' Condition Under the French Colonization,", 1969 January
    - Long, Ngo Vinh, "Tactics and Techniques Used by the U.S. and the NLF in the Context of Vietnamese Society,", undated (Box 117)
    - Moncrief, William H., Jr., "Medical Requirements and Utilization in Less Developed Countries: Republic of Vietnam, 1965-1975,", 1966 March 9
    - Nguyen, Du, The Tale of Kieu, draft of translation by Huynh Sanh Thong, 1970s
    - Pike, Douglas
      - "Life in North Vietnam,", 1972 September
      - "Life in North Vietnam, Part Two: The Law,", 1973 January
      - "The Rebel in North Vietnam,", 1972 July
    - Rambo, A. Terry
      - "The Causes of Refugee Movement in Viet-Nam: Report of a Survey of Refugees in I and IV Corps,", 1968 January
      - "A Comparison of Peasant Social Systems of Northern and Southern Viet-Nam: A Study of Ecological Adaptation, Social Succession, and Cultural Evolution", 1973
      - "The Development of an Open Peasantry on the Lower Mekong Delta Frontier of Viet-Nam: A Case of Social Succession or Evolution?", 1973 March 31
      - "The Dynamics of Refugee Migration in Viet-Nam," thesis, 1969
    - Rambo, A. Terry and Jamieson, Neil L., III, "Cultural Change in Rural Viet-Nam: A Study of the Effects of Long-Term Communist Control on the Social Structure, Attitudes, & Values of the Peasants of the Mekong Delta,", 1970 September
    - Rambo, A. Terry and Jamieson, Neil L., III, "Cultural Change in Rural Viet-Nam: A Study of the Effects of Long-Term Communist Control on the Social Structure, Attitudes, & Values of the Peasants of the Mekong Delta," edited version, circa 1973
    - Rondinelli, Dennis A., "Postwar Reconstruction in Vietnam: The Case for an Urbanization Policy,", 1973 June (Box 118)
    - Silverman, Jerry M., "Vietnam: Official United States Reporting and the Credibility Gap,", 1970
    - Tanter, Raymond, "U.S. Policies, Programs, and Performance in Vietnam,", 1972
    - "Vietnam's Manufacturing Industry: Historical Outline and Development Strategies,", undated
  - VIETNAMESE LANGUAGE MATERIAL, 1960-1973 (Boxes 118-121)
    Contains articles, books, copies of the periodical Công báo Việt Nam Cộng Hoà, á̂n bản Quó̂c hội, and other printed matter in Vietnamese.
  - PRINTED MATTER, 1950-1973, undated (Boxes 122-130, 135)
    Contains books, reports, and other printed matter in English and French. Arranged alphabetically by the organization the work was produced for and then, by author.
    - An Introduction to Vietnam, undated (Box 122)
    - Australia Department of External Affairs, Viet Nam: June 1965 to February 1966, 1966 March
    - Betts, Russell H., Viet Cong Village Control: Some Observations on the Origin and Dynamics of Modern Revolutionary War, 1969
    - Biography and Teachings of Prophet Huynh-Phu-So, 1966
    - Breese, Gerald, ed., Urban Southeast Asia: A Selected Bibliography of Accessible Research, Reports and Related Materials on Urbanism and Urbanization, 1973
    - Chau, Bhikshu Thich Minh, Hsuan Tsang: The Pilgrim and Scholar, 1966
    - Development and Resources Corporation, The Five Northern Provinces of the Republic of Vietnam: Urban Development, 1969 October
    - Dialogue: Addressing to (The Rev.) Martin Luther King, J. P. Sartre, Andre Malraux, Rene Char, and Henry Miller, 1965
    - Doing Business in Vietnam: Legal and Commercial Considerations, 1971
    - Gobron, Gabriel, History and Philosophy of Caodaism, undated
    - Haviland, H. Field, Jr. et al., Vietnam After the War: Peacekeeping and Rehabilitation, 1968 (Box 123)
    - Human Sciences Research Inc. (HSR)
      - Rambo, A. Terry, Tinker, Jerry M., and LeNoir, John D., The Refugee Situation in Phu-Yen Province, Viet-Nam, 1967 July
      - Tinker, Jerry M., The Refugee Situation in Ding Tuong Province, 1967 August
    - Joint Development Group
      - Moore, Frederick T., Economic Policies in the Transition to Peace and After, 1968 June
      - Nguyen, Van Thuan, Nguyen, Cao Dan, and Pressler, Larry L., A Description of Ocean Fish Marketing in Saigon, 1968
      - The Postwar Development of the Republic of Vietnam: Policies and Programs, volumes I and II, 1969 March
      - The Postwar Development of the Republic of Vietnam: Policies and Programs, summary, 1969 March
      - A Program for the Development of the Five Northern Provinces Constituting the I Corps Region of South Vietnam, 1968 December
    - Mai, Trung Tinh, Prose Poems, 1972 (Box 124)
    - Michigan State University Vietnam Advisory Group
      - Hendry, James B., The Work Force in Saigon, photocopy, 1960 February
      - The Study of a Vietnamese Rural Community: Administrative Activity, 1960 May
        Contains a photocopy of select portions of the book.
      - Uong, Ngoc Thach and Cole, David C. Financial Activities of the Provinces, Prefecture and Municipalities of Viet-Nam in 1956, photocopy, 1957
        In Vietnamese and English.
    - Nguyen, Thanh-Nha, Tableau économique du Viêt Nam aux XVIIe et XVIIIe siècles, 1970
    - Phan, The Tran, Anthropologie biochimique du Vietnamien, 1972
    - Phan, Tru'o'ng Manh, A voie du salut Caodaïque, 1950
    - Phong, The, ed., The Voices, 1971
      A collection of poetry translated from Vietnamese by Dam Xuan Can.
    - Quang-Lien, Venerable, A Short Introduction of Buddhism in Vietnam, 1968
    - RAND Corporation
      - Documents
        - Cochran, Samuel W., "Face Validity,", 1968 January 23
        - Cochran, Samuel W. and Jacobsen, Nancy E., "Some Characteristics of the Viet Cong," parts I and II, 1968
        - Cochran Samuel W. and Le-Thi-Que, "Concepts of and Attitudes Toward the VC,", 1967 December 1 (Box 125)
        - Domar, Evsey D., "Agrarian Reform as an Instrument of Revolutionary Warfare,", 1968 May 1
        - Phole, Victoria, "In Retrospect: Views on the RAND Viet Cong Interview Project,", 1968 May 24
        - Stewart, W. A., "Viet Cong Infrastructure: A Semantic Trap,", 1968 March 20
      - Research memoranda
        - Davison, W. P., Some Observations on Viet Cong Operations in the Villages, 1968 May
        - Halpern, A. M. and Fredman, H. B., Communist Strategy in Laos, 1960 June 14
        - Hickey, Gerald C., The Highland People of South Vietnam: Social and Economic Development, 1967 September
        - Mozingo, David P., Sino-Indonesian Relations: An Overview, 1955-1965 (Box 135)
        - Wilson, J. A. and Penzo, M. J., South Vietnam Political Division Tables and Maps, 1964 December (Box 125)
        - Zasloff, J. J., Origins of the Insurgency in South Vietnam, 1954-1960: The Role of the Southern Vietminh Cadres, 1968 May
        - Zasloff, J. J., Political Motivation of the Viet Cong: The Vietminh Regroupees, 1968 May (Box 126)
    - Regional Income of D.C.I. Djakarta 1966-1969, 1971
    - Saigon Metropolitan Area, photocopy, 1965
    - Sherif, Nur, About Arabic Books, 1970
    - South Viet-Nam Background Data, 1971 January
    - South Vietnam Provincial Maps, 1967 September
    - Thich, Duc Nhuan, Buddistic Revelation to the Modern World, undated
    - Truong, Tien Dat, The Constitution of the Republic of Vietnam, photocopy of English translation, undated (Box 127)
    - United States Agency for International Development (USAID)
      - Bush, Henry C., Messegee, Gordon H., and Russell, Roger V., The Impact of the Land to the Tiller Program in the Mekong Delta, 1972 December
      - The Coming Urban Crisis in Asia, 1971 March
      - Dialectics of Urban Proposals for the Saigon Metropolitan Area, 1972 January
      - Galt, Lowell T. and George, William C., Review of Statistical Development in Vietnam - September 1970, 1970 October
      - In Vietnam, a New Rice, New Hope: A Report of the Accelerated Rice Production Program, 1968
      - Ingle, Marcus, Current Village Administration, 1970
      - Laws and Other Legal Directives Governing the Province, Municipal and Village Budgets and Local Taxes and Other Revenues in Vietnam, 1970 September
      - "Listing of Studies and Reports (Vietnam) Financed or Prepared by A.I.D.,", 1972
      - National Power Survey of the Republic of Vietnam, 1972 February
      - Operational Report FY 1963-1964, circa 1964
      - Progress Report: Saigon Land Use Survey, photocopy, 1970 February (Box 128)
      - Public Administration in the Saigon Metropolitan Area, 1963
      - Report: U.S. Support of Public Building Construction in Viet Nam and the Directorate General of Reconstruction and Urban Planning's Public Building Process, photocopy, 1970 June
      - Report of the Social Welfare Task Force to USAID/VN USAID/W, 1967
      - Report of the Social Welfare Task Force to USAID/VN USAID/W, 1969
      - Report on Social Security in Vietnam, 1969
      - Report to the Ambassador from the Director of the United States Agency for International Development, Vietnam, 1967-1969
      - "The Republic of Vietnam: The Code of Civil and Commercial Procedure (Draft)," unofficial translation, 1968
      - "The Republic of Vietnam: The Code of Criminal Procedure (Draft),", 1968
      - "The Republic of Vietnam: The Commercial Code (Draft)," unofficial translation, 1968
      - "[The Republic of Vietnam]: Draft of the Criminal Code," unofficial translation, 1969 (Box 129)
      - "The Republic of Vietnam: Draft of Proposed Civil Code,", 1968 March
      - Review of Certain Problems Relating to Administration of the Economic and Technical Assistance Program for Viet Nam 1958-1962, report to the Congress of the United States, 1964 July
      - Saigon Metropolitan Area Land Use Survey, 1972 May 15
      - Salter, MacDonald, Land reform in South Vietnam: Spring Review, 1970 (Box 135)
      - Stroup, Robert H., Rural Income and Expenditure Sample Survey of Vietnam (Initial Report), 1967 July (Box 129)
      - U.S. Foreign Aid in Vietnam: Proposed Fiscal Year 1972 Program
      - Urban Planning in Vietnam: Phase I, photocopy, 1968
      - Urban Planning in Vietnam: Phase II, 1970
      - Year 2000 Population Projections for Republic of Vietnam and Saigon Metropolitan Area, 1971 March
    - United States Department of State
      - Viet-Nam Information Notes, number 6, 1967 June
      - Viet-Nam Post Report, 1971 July
      - Vietnamese Basic Course, volume I, 1967
    - United States Mission in Vietnam
      - The New Statute on Agricultural Cooperatives: In the Context of the Agricultural Policy Debate in North Viet Nam, 1969 October (Box 130)
      - Viet-Nam Documents and Research Notes, 1968, 1971
        Contains Documents 30-32, "After Tet: Three Viet Cong Assessments;" Document 96, "The Viet-Nam Workers' Party's 1963 Decision to Escalate the War in the South;" and Document 108, "PRP Abandons 1972 Plans for a Revolution in Saigon." See also Formerly Closed Material.